[
  {
    "question": "According to Monroe C. Beardsley, can a toaster be considered a work of art?",
    "answers": ["Yes, if it is intended to satisfy aesthetic preferences."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill the blank Berys Gaut argues against a global theory of interpretation in his essay \"Interpreting the Arts: The Patchwork Theory\" because:...",
    "answers": [
      "The text itself can contribute to meaning, regardless of authorial intent."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approach to determining the meaning of a literary work does Jerrold Levinson advocate for?",
    "answers": ["Utterance meaning"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which theory does Berys Gaut challenge in his essay 'Interpreting the Arts: The Patchwork Theory'?",
    "answers": ["Global theory of interpretation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to Paul Ziff, can a true definition of art be found?",
    "answers": ["No."]
  },
  {
    "question": "How does Levinson define a new work of art?",
    "answers": ["Its relationship with pre-existing art."]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to George Dickie, what factor constitutes a work of art?",
    "answers": ["The recognition by the art world."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approach does Berys Gaut advocate for in interpretation theories?",
    "answers": ["Hypothetical intentionalism"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to R. G. Collingwood, what makes true art?",
    "answers": ["Showcase the artist's skills"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which film does Carroll use as an example to discuss the idea of subversive filmmaking?",
    "answers": ["\"Plan 9 From Outer Space\""]
  }
]
